<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PathPiolet</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions">TERMS &amp; CONDITIONS\n\n1. Acceptance of Terms\nBy accessing and using PathPoilet, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. Our platform provides educational roadmaps and college recommendations for informational purposes.\n\n2. Nature of Guidance\nThe roadmaps, career paths, and college suggestions provided by PathPoilet are generated based on industry trends and educational data. While we strive for accuracy, these should be used as a guide only. Final decisions regarding your education and career should be made after independent research and professional consultation.\n\n3. Data Accuracy\nCollege fees, NIRF rankings, and placement data are subject to change. PathPoilet does not guarantee the real-time accuracy of these values. Users are encouraged to verify details from official institute websites.\n\n4. User Content\nUsers are responsible for the accuracy of information provided during profile setup and preference selection. Misleading information may result in inaccurate recommendations.\n\n5. Limitation of Liability\nPathPoilet shall not be liable for any educational or career setbacks resulting from the use of our recommendations. Our goal is to assist, but success depends on individual effort and external factors.\n\n6. Changes to Terms\nWe reserve the right to modify these terms at any time. Continued use of the app implies acceptance of the updated terms.</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">PRIVACY POLICY\n\n1. Information Collection\nPathPoilet collects basic user information including name, email, education level, and career interests. This data is essential to provide personalized roadmaps and relevant college suggestions.\n\n2. Use of Information\nYour data is used to:\n- Generate custom career roadmaps.\n- Filter college recommendations based on your preferences.\n- Send reminders for important exam dates.\n- Improve our matching algorithms.\n\n3. Data Storage\nAll user data is stored securely in our private backend database. We implement industry-standard security measures to protect your information from unauthorized access.\n\n4. Data Sharing\nPathPoilet does NOT sell, trade, or share your personal information with third-party marketing companies. Your data remains strictly within our ecosystem for the sole purpose of enhancing your experience.\n\n5. User Control\nYou have the right to update your profile information at any time through the app settings. Deleting your account will result in the permanent removal of your personal data from our systems.\n\n6. Policy Updates\nWe may update this policy periodically. Notifications of significant changes will be provided within the app.</string>
</resources>